If you pay attention to the things that shine forth
because what you're seeing is the reality instead of the map
you're gaining access to the real information that's in the world
it's not prepackaged information, because that can be false
it's the real information flowing out from the ground of being
and if you pay attention to that, it will help you move towards the goals
that you've already established for yourself as a good citizen, that are part of the inbuilt value structure
that you've adopted. But at the same time it will do something else it will lead you to
transform the nature of those goals because as you pursue the thing that guides your interest and
more and more information is revealed then by absorbing that Information which is learning essentially
you build yourself into a different person a stronger and more Informed person and a more
intact person a person with more integrity and with more strength and with more direction
and at the same time you differentiate your map and so you're living more and more in the real world
so as you approach your specific goal even if it's a culturally conditioned goal
the learning that you do along the way transforms you and it transforms the nature of your goal.